Jhaal we will
overcome this difficult time by shouting from the heart
call ji closer to you
India has never lost and will never lose this fight
we will go to this thing our duty will remain agriculture which was
Meena see a lot of media life astrology
when it seems better to go to the mountains but you keep courage keep your
steps down it is in everyone's account it is just for a few
days fight courage depth om saaf on
Thursday we will win ee ee
good we are yours we will win as much as we can we will win
this we have won whoever really has taken the
responsibility of the country's security the
doctors and police are not to help me we will dance and hum in the same way you will make
everyone laugh
in the festivals the bathrooms in the streets
you will again make noise Medicare
we will understand this serious topic how to
mix with a wonder
committee that you have so much
wheat
that you are so good now the
increase in the number of crops which have probably doubled that it is in
all of us
[Music]
MP3